Thankgod Onwubuali

Wordpress Developer

Lagos, Nigeria innovationinflesh@gmail.com +234 907 085 6284

I am a Wordpress Developer with interest in human centered solutions. My technical expertise spams through years of experience with solving problems using PHP, JavaScripts and jQuery on WordPress.

I have been a full stack WordPress developer for the past few years, I specialise in designing and building awesome user interfaces while maintaining the product's scope.

I'm open to opportunities and gigs that's boost career growth.

Let's work together!

Work Experience

CTO (Wordpress Developer)

Farmpaddi - Abia January 2021 to Present

Responsible for developing and managing the startup website, designing appealing webpages and interacting on a daily basis with other developers and users.

CTO (Wordpress Developer)

Markchart Logistics - Lagos January 2020 to December 2020

Worked as the CTO at the lagos based logistics company, carrying out IT Manager tasks as requested. Had a specific brief to ensure the company website and social presence brought in quality customers.

- Developing and maintaining the front end and back end functionality of website.
- Participating in discussions with clients to clarify what they want.
- Designing prototypes for app and website.
- Creating logos, banners and buttons for website.
- Writing cross-browser compliant HTML, CSS & JavaScript.
- Simultaneously managing several databases and reporting tools.
- Contacting external webmasters to confirm link placements.
- Provide guidance to other team members on web development issues.
- Developing websites that have a consistent feel and look throughout all web properties.
- Providing technical support to end users. Identifying and correcting software deficiencies.
- Devising SEO strategies based around specific keywords

Wordpress Developer (REMOTE)

Deeg Web - Lagos February 2019 to December 2019 At Deeg Web, i was responsible for working on a range of projects, designing appealing websites and interacting on a daily basis with graphic designers, developers and business owners.

Education

Undergraduate in Civil Engineering

Micheal Okpara University of Agriculture Umudike - Umuahia October 2015 to October 2020

Skills

- WordPress Development (5 years)
- WordPress Design (5 years)
- Javascript (4 years)
- HTML/CSS (6 years)
- Search Engine Optimization (3 years)
- Web Graphics (3 years)
- Bootstrap (3 years)
- HTML5 (2 years)
- PHP (3 years)
- MySQL (4 years)